<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<abstract>
    <para>This guide describes how to get started with eXo Platform 3.5, especially for:</para>
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          <emphasis role="bold">System Administrators</emphasis> who want to use, deploy and manage the eXo Platform system in their enterprises.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          <emphasis role="bold">Developers</emphasis> who want to know how to leverage eXo Platform in their customer projects.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
	<para>Throughout the guide, you can do many administrative tasks when implementing eXo Platform 3.5. The administration of eXo Platform 3.5 is categorized into the following chapters:</para>
	<itemizedlist>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Installation_and_Startup">Installation and Startup</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Information about system requirements and profiles, as well as how to install the Tomcat bundle and JBoss EARs.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Configuration">Configuration</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Understanding of configuration related to database, cache, users and gadget proxy, file system paths, mail server, WebDAV Cache Control, Chat Server, OpenOffice Server, Logs, JCR.
			</para>
		</listitem>
        <listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Deployment">Deployment</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				How-Tos of removing sample applications, deploying a custom extension, setting up Apache Front-end and configuring the session timeout for the web server.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Management">Management</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Introduction to the eXo Platform management views.
			</para>
		</listitem>
        <listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Clustering">Clustering</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Changes related to clustering, which are necessary for eXo Platform to work in the cluster mode.
			</para>
		</listitem>
        <listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Integration">Organization Integration</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Instructions on how to connect eXo Platform to a populated data source, such as LDAP server, MS ActiveDirectory, or Database.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Backup">Backup and Restore</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Backup of database and file systems for the JCR index and value storage.
			</para>
		</listitem>
        <listitem>
			<para>
				<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Security">Security</link></emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Changes related to the JAAS realm.
			</para>
		</listitem>
	</itemizedlist>
</abstract>