<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<preface xml:id="AboutAdministratorGuide">
<title>About this guide</title>
<abstract>
    <para>This guide describes how to get started with eXo Platform 3.5, especially for:</para>
    <itemizedlist>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          <emphasis role="bold">System Administrators</emphasis> who want to use, deploy and manage the eXo Platform system in their enterprises.</para>
      </listitem>
      <listitem>
        <para>
          <emphasis role="bold">Developers</emphasis> who want to know how to leverage eXo Platform in their customer projects.</para>
      </listitem>
    </itemizedlist>
<para>Through the guide, you can do many administrative tasks when implementing eXo Platform 3.5. The administration of eXo Platform 3.5 is categorized into the following main topics:</para>
<itemizedlist>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Installation_and_Startup">Installation and Startup</link></emphasis>: Knowledge of how to install the Tomcat bundle and JBoss EARs and information of eXo Platform profiles.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Configuration">Configuration</link></emphasis>: Understanding of configuration related to eXo Platform, database, cache, users and gadget proxy, file system paths, mail server, WebDAV Cache Control, Chat Server, OpenOffice Server, Log-in, JCR.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Management">Management</link></emphasis>: Introduction to eXo Platform management, knowledge of eXo Platform management views.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Security">Security</link></emphasis>: Changes related to the JAAS realm.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Backup">Backup and Restore</link></emphasis>: Backup of database and file systems for the JCR index and value storage.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Clustering">Clustering</link></emphasis>: Changes related to clustering, which are necessary for eXo Platform to work in the cluster mode.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Deployment">Deployment</link></emphasis>: How-Tos of removing sample applications, deploying a custom extension, setting up Apache Front-end and configuring the session timeout for the web server.
</para>
</listitem>
<listitem>
<para>
<emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="ADM.Integration">Organization Integration</link></emphasis>: Instructions on how to connect eXo Platform to a populated data source, such as LDAP server, MS ActiveDirectory, or Database.
</para>
</listitem>
</itemizedlist>
</abstract>
</preface>