<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<abstract>
<para>The intended readers of this document are users using eXo Platform. This user guide explains all the basic and advanced features of eXo Platform by providing a series of in-depth examples and clear explanations which help users easily benefit from the eXo Platform capabilities and features. </para>
 <para>After reading this guide, developers are expected to be able to customize their own portals and 
develop applications to run on eXo Platform 3.5 through the following topics:</para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.GetStarted">Get Started</link>:
              </emphasis>Introduction to terms commonly used, how to set up Maven settings and eXo Architecture Primer.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.CreatingYourOwnPortal">Create Your Own Portal</link>:
              </emphasis>Steps on how to create and customize your own portal.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.WorkingwithContent">Work With Content</link>:
              </emphasis>Topics related to the eXo Platform content.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.WorkingwithApplications">Work With Applications</link>:
              </emphasis>Instructions on how to integrate applications into your portal and how to deploy your own applications.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.SystemIntegration">System Integration</link>:
              </emphasis>Topics related to the eXo Platform 3.5 integration into information systems through specific topics, such as authentication, user integration, LDAP integration and Email configuration.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.SystemIntegration">System Integration</link>:
              </emphasis>Introduction to terms commonly used, how to set up Maven settings and eXo Architecture Primer.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.eXoPlatformAPIs">eXo Platform 3.5 APIs</link>:
              </emphasis>Information of APIs.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.Cookbook">Cookbook</link>:
              </emphasis>Introduction to Cookbook, particularly steps on how to copy a site to another eXo Platform server.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.Upgrade">Upgrade eXo Platform</link>:
              </emphasis>Steps on how to upgrade eXo Platform from 3.0 to 3.5, especially when your system is an extension of eXo Platform 3.0 with many customizations related to configurations, components and added features.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
</abstract>