<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<abstract>
<para>The guide you are reading is intended to be a rich introduction to the depth of <emphasis role="bold">eXo Platform</emphasis>. 
As a developer, you can use this guide to have a solid framework for achieving your goals on the platform. Throughout this guide,
you will meet a high-level tour of eXo Platform and its capabilities via the following chapters:
</para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.GetStarted">Get Started</link>
			  </emphasis>	
			</para>	
			<para>
              An introduction to terms commonly used, the process to set up Maven settings and understanding of eXo Architecture Primer.
			</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.CreatingYourOwnPortal">Create Your Own Portal</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
			A procedure that instructs you to create your extension project, define a default portal and its structure, manage languages, create a custom look and feel, add JavaScript, or create custom templates.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.WorkingwithContent">Work With Content</link>
			  </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Topics which are related to creating a new content manually in eXo Platform, such as node type, dialog syntax, CKEditor, taxonomy, template service or Navigation By Content.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.WorkingwithApplications">Work With Applications</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
			  Instructions on how to integrate, then to deploy an application into your portal.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.SystemIntegration">System Integration</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Topics related to the eXo Platform 3.5 integration into information systems through specific topics, such as authentication, user integration, LDAP integration and Email configuration.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.SystemIntegration">System Integration</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Information of authentication and users integration, details of numerous parameters of the eXo LDAP organization service, and the way to configure the email service.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.eXoPlatformAPIs">eXo Platform 3.5 APIs</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Definitions of API levels, and a list of eXo Platform APIs and provisional APIs.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.Cookbook">Cookbook</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				Steps on how to copy a site to another eXo Platform server.
			</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="DEV.Upgrade">Upgrade eXo Platform</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>
				All requirements, what needs to be prepared/adapted in eXo Platform extension, and how to update Maven dependencies, configurations, components and extensions.
			</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
</abstract>