<abstract>
<para>The intended readers of this document are users using eXo Platform. This user guide explains all the basic and advanced features of eXo Platform by providing a series of in-depth examples and clear explanations which help users easily benefit from the eXo Platform capabilities and features. </para>
 <para>This documentation is divided into the following chapters:</para>
        <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Get_started">Get Started</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>A list of glossaries commonly used in applications of eXo Platform, interface of eXo Platform 3.5, and how to manage your accounts and language.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Manage_Organization">Manage Your Organization</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>Instructions on how to manage users, groups and memberships in eXo Platform.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Manage_Your_Portals">Manage Your Portals</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>A collection of portal-based actions, allowing you to manage permissions, sites/portals, navigation nodes, pages and applications.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Organize_Content">Organize Your Content</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>Instructions on how to structure your content, manage content, newsletters and workflows.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Collaboration">Collaborate With Your Colleagues</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>Instructions on how to perform actions to enhance communication and collaboration through emails, address books, chat and calendars.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Knowledge">Organize Your Knowledge</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>Instructions on how to perform actions in Wiki, Forum, and FAQs.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="Platform_User_Guide.Social">Build Social Network</link>
              </emphasis>
			</para>
			<para>Instructions on how to manage your profiles and spaces, build networks and follow activities in your network.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
</abstract>