<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!DOCTYPE book PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DocBook XML V4.5//EN" "http://www.oasis-open.org/docbook/xml/4.5/docbookx.dtd">
<book xml:id="Overview">
    <title>Overview</title>
<chapter id="AbouteXoPlatform">
	<title>About eXo Platform</title>
      <!--<section>-->
      <para>
	  eXo Platform is the first and only integrated, cloud-ready user experience platform for building and deploying transactional websites, managing web and social content and creating gadgets and dashboards. 
	  eXo Platform lets companies leverage their existing Java infrastructure, while accommodating changing user behavior driven by consumer web technologies, such as social networks, social publishing and forums.
	  </para>
	  <para>
	  The following illustration gives you the overall architecture of eXo Platform 3.5.
	  </para>
	  <mediaobject>
        <imageobject role="html">
          <imagedata fileref="images/Architecture_PLF3.png" format="PNG" align="center" scale="110"/>
        </imageobject>
        <imageobject role="fo">
          <imagedata fileref="images/Architecture_PLF3.png" format="PNG" align="center" scalefit="1" contentwidth="100mm"/>
        </imageobject>
      </mediaobject>
	  <para>
	  The foundation of eXo Platform 3.5 is an enterprise portal and content management system. This provides a powerful set of REST-based services for rapid website development, content management and gadget-based development and deployment. 
	  eXo Platform 3.5 includes the following features.
	  </para>
	  <itemizedlist>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			An enterprise portal serves as a powerful framework for developing portlets and other web-based user interfaces, and is based on the open source GateIn portal project co-developed by eXo and Red Hat.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			Web Content Management extends portal-based applications, allowing you to build dynamic and content-rich websites.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			Document Management for capturing and organizing documents and unstructured content, with content storage in the built-in Java Content Repository (JCR).
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			xCMIS is an implementation of the full stack of Java-based CMIS (Content Management Interoperability Specification) services, so eXo-based applications can integrate with existing content management tools.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			Business Process Management (BPM) from Bonita Open Solution enables you to define workflow processes with automatic actions for web content, documents and more.
			</para>
		</listitem>
		<listitem>
			<para>
			Cloud-ready features allow eXo Platform 3.5 to run in multi-tenant environments, so social intranets and websites can take advantage of the benefits of private and public cloud platforms.
			</para>
		</listitem>
	  </itemizedlist>
	  <para>
	  With eXo Platform 3.5, you can customize and extend your portal-based applications with user experience services to build social intranets and extranets.
	  </para>
	  <itemizedlist>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		Enterprise social network features allow users to connect, collaborate within dedicated spaces, and publish real-time updates in activity streams. 
		Support for OpenSocial provides a framework for building gadgets that can display and mash up activity information for contacts, social networks, applications and services.
		</para>
	  </listitem>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		Collaboration &amp; communication tools let you build a more productive and interactive dashboard for social intranet users. Intuitive Mail, Chat, Calendar and Address Book functionalities can seamlessly extend your portal-based web applications.
		</para>
	  </listitem>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		Knowledge management features, including Forums, Answers, FAQs, and a complete enterprise wiki, can transform an extranet into an interactive online community and valuable knowledge base.
	    </para>
	  </listitem>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		Custom development in the web-based IDE is an intuitive web-based development environment where you can build, test and deploy client applications, such as gadgets and mash-ups, and RESTful services online. 
		Offering the ability to extend eXo Platform online, eXo IDE instantly publishes any application that you can create and deploy immediately in your portal-based solutions.
	    </para>
	  </listitem>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		CRaSH is an open source tool to view and query content within a JCR server at runtime. It enables you to browse JCR trees, and serves as a shell for executing JCR operations easily, such as importing or exporting data securely. 
		You can now extend the shell by writing Groovy commands, without recompiling easily.
	    </para>
	  </listitem>
	  <listitem>
		<para>
		Native mobile applications for iPhone, iPad and Android allow users to easily and securely access their personalized intranet dashboards, activity streams, documents and more.
		</para>
      </listitem>
	 </itemizedlist>
	 <!--</section>-->
   </chapter>

  <chapter id="BrowserCompatibility">
    <title>Browser compatibility</title>
  <para>eXo Platform 3.5 is designed to work within an Internet browser, and we have made every effort to make eXo Platform 3.5 compatible with as many of common web browsers as possible.</para>
  <para>
    This product has been thoroughly tested on the following stable browsers:
  </para>
  <itemizedlist>
    <listitem>
      <para>Internet Explorer 7, 8, and 9</para>
    </listitem>
    <listitem>
      <para>Firefox 3.5, 3.6, and 4</para>
    </listitem>
  </itemizedlist>
    <para>
      Unfortunately, we have not been able to make this product compatible will all browsers. Therefore, we strongly
      recommend that you use the browsers listed above. In case of any questions, please contact your administrator.
    </para>
  </chapter>
</book>
