<?xml version='1.0' encoding='utf-8' ?>
<abstract>
<para>The intended readers of this document are developers using eXo Platform. This document provides developers, and even beginners with the
  comprehensive knowledge of eXo JCR which is a powerful open source implementation of the <ulink url="http://jcp.org/en/jsr/detail?id=170">Java Specification Request 170</ulink>
  also known as the Content Repository for Java technology API. </para>
 <para>It is expected you will be able to use your gained knowledge here either for portlet development or as the first step to bundle eXo Portlet Container with your own Portal implementation to reach compliance with JSR 168 and JSR 286.</para>
  <para>The guide is divided into the following chapters:</para>
  <itemizedlist>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="chapter-JCR">eXo JCR</link>:</emphasis> Instructions on how to configure and use eXo JCR in GateIn and standalone.</para>
          </listitem>
          <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="chapter-Kernel">eXo Kernel</link>:</emphasis> Topics on eXo Kernel that is the basis of all eXo platform products and modules. The Kernel module also contains a set of very low level services, therefore throughout this chapter, beginners can gain the most basic knowledge of the service configuration.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="chapter-eXoCore">eXo Core</link>:</emphasis> The comprehensive knowledge of eXo Core and how to use its services.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold">
                <link linkend="chapter-eXoWS">eXo Web Services</link>:</emphasis> Topics on the eXo Web Services module that allows eXo technology to integrate with external products and services.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="chapter-eXoJCRWithGateIn">eXo JCR with GateIn</link>:</emphasis> Instructions on how to extend your GateIn instance, and how to use AS Managed DataSource under JBoss AS.</para>
          </listitem>
		  <listitem>
            <para>
              <emphasis role="bold"><link linkend="chapter-FrequentlyAskedQuestion">Frequently Asked Question</link>:</emphasis> A list of all FAQs related to Kernel, JCR core, JCR extensions, WebDAV, and more.</para>
          </listitem>
        </itemizedlist>
</abstract>